Player_FinalAssignment_01DLG01=Holy shit… Holy fucking shit…
Player_FinalAssignment_01DLG02=Hey, anybody there? Brother?
Mother_FinalAssignment_01DLG03=More fighting… More death. I can't let this happen again… I won't…
Player_FinalAssignment_01DLG04=It's… It's you? Where are the Faceless? What's happening to me, why do I hear your voice inside my head?!
Mother_FinalAssignment_01DLG05=Children of the Sun, Kyle… They were nothing before the outbreak. Just a half-forgotten tradition… An old-world faith long dead…
Mother_FinalAssignment_01DLG06=I'm tired. I've held this title for so long now. The Mother. It was meaningless… Until it became all too real.
Mother_FinalAssignment_01DLG07=I thought their respect came simply because I was a colonel's wife. We had a good, cozy life…
Mother_FinalAssignment_01DLG08=After the outbreak my husband came to get me out. We didn't stand a chance against the horde. We were bitten. He bled to death in my arms.
Mother_FinalAssignment_01DLG09=He gave me his cigarette case and asked me to run. He didn't want to hurt me. I was dragged away by the believers… They came for their Mother.
CIN_TheMotherB_01_Player=So what…that's it? Game over…? Fuck… Fuck! All right. So what do I do?
CIN_TheMotherB_02_Mother=Wake up the God of the Sun. Follow me, Kyle.
CIN_TheMotherB_03_Player=So the coming of your God means… We all die? And the plague – it dies with us?
CIN_TheMotherB_04_Mother=It always meant that. "…and He shall pass through the Gates of Death so that He may bring new life".
CIN_TheMotherB_05_Player=If it kills the plague… I mean… I guess it's worth it. This place doesn't look much like the 'Gates of Death' to me, though.
CIN_TheMotherB_06_Mother=Flowery language, isn't it? I was searching for proof, Kyle. For truth in our traditions. But Atilla's death shattered my hopes. It was proof.
CIN_TheMotherB_07_Player=What? That there are no miracles?
CIN_TheMotherB_08_Mother=What's a miracle, anyway, Kyle? Becoming a sentient Volatile? I'm nothing more than a monster. Becoming a hero during the apocalypse? You're just the right man in the right place.
CIN_TheMotherB_09_Player=Yeah, and I was almost convinced I was the God of the Sun.
CIN_TheMotherB_10_Mother=You're a decent human being, Kyle… But today you will get the chance to play god.
Player_TheMotherB_01DLG01=…So this is the "fail-safe". And what do you need me for?
Mother_TheMotherB_01DLG02=The key I got from my husband worked. But the codes he gave me didn't. I know that's the only way, I just don't know how.
Player_TheMotherB_01DLG03=Codes…
Mother_FinalAssignment_08DLG01=The fumes are powerful here, aren't they?
Mother_FinalAssignment_08DLG02=They penetrate the skin… The bones… The brain.
Mother_FinalAssignment_08DLG03=I hear your thoughts, Kyle. Your fear.
Mother_FinalAssignment_08DLG09=I'm coming for you.
