Camden_Clinic_02DLG01=I was sad to hear about Dr. Zere. He and I were thrilled to get the chance to study the Harran Virus…
Camden_Clinic_02DLG02=Not to mention, the GRE paid us quite handsomely.
Camden_Clinic_02DLG03=By the way, we’re on backup power now, so we have minimal functionality.
Camden_Clinic_02DLG04=I needed extra power for my last experiment and the generators overheated and shut down.
Camden_Clinic_03DLG01=I hope you don’t mind me reminiscing out loud like this. It’s been quite a number of weeks since I’ve had the prospect of talking to an actual live human, in person.
Camden_Clinic_03DLG02=Oh - and the door leading to the main corridor can only be opened manually. You’ll have to get to the security room and throw the switch.
Player_Clinic_03DLG03=On my way.
Camden_Clinic_04DLG01=All right, now go down the main corridor. The lab is on the left.
Camden_Clinic_04DLG02=When the outbreak happened, Zere and I stayed in the quarantine to work on the cure. You know who was supposed to protect us? Kadir Suleiman! Rais himself!
Camden_Clinic_04DLG03=THAT worked out just perfectly.
Camden_Clinic_06DLG01=Okay. The only way into the lab is through the decontamination room. The entrance is to the right.
Camden_Clinic_06DLG02=Everything went straight to hell after Rais’s brother died, you know. Rais went from a guy with monstrous tendencies to a full-blown monster.
Camden_Clinic_07DLG02=You’ll have to run the decontamination protocol to unlock the doors.
Camden_Clinic_07DLG03=It won’t work without full power, though. That’s where the generators come in.
Camden_Clinic_07DLG05=Head to the offices. Once you’re there, I’ll point you in the right direction.
Player_Clinic_07DLG055=All right, I’m on it…
Camden_Clinic_07DLG06=Zere and I got to safety with the help of a GRE operative - a man very similar to you…
Camden_Clinic_08DLG01=The operative who helped us was supposed to evacuate alongside us… but you can guess how well that worked out, since Zere and I both got stuck here.
Camden_Clinic_08DLG02=Be extra careful, now - I never cleared the Infected from that part of the facility, as I’ve never had a reason to go in there.
Camden_Clinic_09DLG02=Watch it - I’m opening the door.
Camden_Clinic_09DLG01=I got separated from the two of them, but I made it here, to this clinic. I really had no other option than to work on finding a cure.
Camden_Clinic_10DLG01=Zere and the operative fell in with Brecken’s crowd. I guess I would have as well, if I’d been able to get to them.
Camden_Clinic_10DLG02=Hmm… I’m sorry about this, but the only way to get to the generator room is through the ventilation shafts.
Camden_Clinic_10DLG04=The shafts lead to the stockroom. From there you can reach the hallway and then the generators.
Camden_Clinic_11DLG02=Good job. Now head back to the decontamination room.
Camden_Clinic_11DLG03=You know, I suspect, even if Zere had been able to leave the quarantine, he wouldn’t have. He and the operative both felt the need to stay and help people.
Camden_Clinic_12DLG01=Push the button by the door to begin the process.
Camden_Clinic_13DLG01=All right. Now you can come in.
