Player_Bunker_03DLG01=Thabit. Are you listening?
Thabit_Bunker_03DLG02=If you’re in the Town Hall, could you filch me some stationary from City Council President’s chambers?
Player_Bunker_03DLG03=Where’s the pass card to enter the bunker?
Thabit_Bunker_03DLG04=The pass card, of course!
Thabit_Bunker_03DLG05=Do to a series of tragic events, the chain of custody of that card has frequently changed, but I believe it finally landed in the capable hands of Police Captain Halim.
Thabit_Bunker_03DLG06=That’s who you need to get it from.
Player_Bunker_03DLG07=Why hasn’t he opened the bunker himself?
Thabit_Bunker_03DLG08=Regretfully, Captain Halim’s interest in material things is no more. He frequently shambles around K-Street, with several other former police officers.
Thabit_Bunker_03DLG09=Perhaps they have some vague recollection of their fraternity.
Thabit_Bunker_05DLG01=By order of the Mayor, the entire contents of this bunker now belongs to me!
Thabit_Bunker_05DLG02=Get away from it, thief!
Player_Bunker_END01=Ihsan, this is Crane. I’m in a supply bunker, under the Town Hall. I think we hit the jackpot.
Ihsan_Bunker_END02=That’s great news, Crane. Thank you. Did you actually get Thabit to help you?
Player_Bunker_END03=Yeah, but I had to kill him in the end.
Ihsan_Bunker_END04=I totally understand.
