Player_Ghost_02DLG01=Let’s see what this says.
BoyGhost_Ghost_03DLG01=Ekhem, ekhem, … Detective Dooley and his assistant begin their search for: The Missing Person of Dolma Street!
BoyGhost_Ghost_03DLG02=Oh, Come on! You have to help me! Dad’s been out all day. Come on! We’re going to find him.
BoyGhost_Ghost_03DLG03=Ehem… The missing person of interest went out very normally to get some food, only to become missing under mysterious circumstances.
BoyGhost_Ghost_03DLG04=Detectives Mike and Tom Dooley are sent to look for clues in the other apartments.
Player_Ghost_04DLG01=Alright, boys, you were playing detective. What happened next?
Player_Ghost_10DLG01=Nothing here…
Player_Ghost_11DLG01=This place is empty…
Player_Ghost_13DLG01=Okay, what now…
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG01=Flat number three is locked. Maybe the strange man who lives here has seen something. Or maybe he saw too much!
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG02=We will interrogate him later…
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG03=Hey, where’re you going?! … Wait! Wait for me!
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG04=Detective Dooley’s partner has left the area of investigation, no doubt in pursuit of some clue.
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG05=It appears that he’s gone down to the basement. I’m following his lead now.
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG06=Detective Dooley reporting. I’m entering the basement to check the trace.
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG07=Mike! Are you here?
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG08=Mike? Is that you?
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG09=Mike!!! Miiike!!!!!!
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG10=Miiike! Mike!!…
BoyGhost_Ghost_05DLG11=Aaaaaaaaa!!!!!!
Player_Ghost_06DLG01=Oh, Jesus…
Player_Ghost_07DLG01=Then that was Mike…
Umar_Ghost_08DLG01=Meat! … Meat! … Meat! … Meat!
Player_Ghost_09DLG01=Case closed.
Rupert_FindRupert_NEA01=Who are you?
Rupert_FindRupert_NEA02=What are you doing here?
Rupert_FindRupert_NEA03=Hold it right there.
Player_FindRupert_01DLG02=I’m Crane. I was looking for Rupert.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG03=No, you weren’t. You were looking for a gunsmith, who happens to be named Rupert.
Player_FindRupert_01DLG04=Fair enough. I’d like to talk about some weapon modifications.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG05=You work for Rais?
Player_FindRupert_01DLG06=No.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG07=Well, I suppose that helps. But I’m waiting for my wife Jasmine to come back. Until she’s here, I can’t leave.
Player_FindRupert_01DLG08=Has she been gone long?
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG09=No. Not long. So, it’ll probably be a while before she returns.
Player_FindRupert_01DLG10=And what about these kids, are their parents… ?
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG11=Dead, I hope. Every day I’m terrified that one of them is going to look out the window, and see their mother or father shambling down the street.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG12=I don’t know what I’m going to do when that happens.
Player_FindRupert_01DLG13=What have you told them?
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG14=Half-truths, that a dark magic has taken over the city, but that I'm a good wizard, who can protect them. It's the sort of game that doesn't end.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG15=Jasmine is better at this sort of thing. Hell, I’m a gunsmith. What am I doing playing this magical nonsense?
Player_FindRupert_01DLG16=Seems to me you’re doing pretty well.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG17=Well, I’m not. There’s a girl named Alya. She’s a diabetic, only her insulin ran out a while ago. Now her blood sugar is sky high.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG18=She’s dehydrated and exhausted. Jasmine says if she doesn’t get some insulin soon, she’ll slip into a coma and die.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG19=And here I am in this stupid wizard hat, and the kids are waiting for me to cure her with a magic potion. Maybe it’s time to tell them the truth.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG20=There is no good magic. Only the dark kind.
Player_FindRupert_01DLG21=Take it easy, Rupert. There’s a drug store in town. Maybe I could find some insulin there.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG22=Are you serious? Mister, if you could do that, I can’t tell you how grateful I’d be.
Rupert_FindRupert_01DLG23=I’ve got a radio here. If my wife Jasmine comes back, I’ll probably go home for a while. But I’ll let you know before I leave.
Rupert_HealthPotion_END01=I can’t believe you’ve done it!
Player_HealthPotion_END02=Will she be alright?
Rupert_HealthPotion_END03=Yes-yes, it’s exactly what she needs.
Rupert_HealthPotion_END04=I’ll take care of Alya, but could you keep the other children busy while I’m with her?
Player_HealthPotion_END05=Well, I’m really… I’m pretty busy.
Rupert_HealthPotion_END06=Just talk to them. That’s all you need to do. I’ve already told them you’re a great warrior. Like a knight.
Player_HealthPotion_END07=You did? When’s your wife coming back?
Rupert_HealthPotion_END08=You’ll be fine. I just need a few minutes.
Rupert_HealthPotion_END09=Children! This heroic warrior has returned with a healing elixir for Alya!
Children_HealthPotion_END10=YEA!!!
Rupert_HealthPotion_END11=Now he’s going to stay here and be your protector, while I administer the elixir to Alya
Player_HealthPotion_END12=Well, hang on, now wait…
Rupert_HealthPotion_END13=I won’t be long.
Collectable_BricksForTheBoy_Diary01=21 June - Rupert is so sweet to me. Tonight he pulled out the photo album of our honeymoon in Budapest. I know he’s trying to take my mind of what’s happening to me. And it worked. For a while. But he can’t stay awake forever, and without him to talk to, I can’t help dwelling on it. We’ve started talking about what we’ll need to do. When the time comes.
Collectable_BricksForTheBoy_Diary02=22 June - Things are starting to get cloudy for me. I guess that’s the best way to put it. I’m having terrible mood swings, and for a minute today I didn’t even recognize my husband. We both know what needs to happen. And it’s not as though he doesn’t have plenty of guns. He can find one that will do the job almost instantly. No suffering. Part of me wants him to go ahead and do it right now. But then, I want to cherish every possible moment I can have with him. My poor, dear man. I know I’m asking a lot. I hope it’s not too much.
Collectable_BricksForTheBoy_Diary03=23 June - Today is my last day. I know it is. I know Rupert has to do it today. We have to say goodbye… and he has to grant me the peace I’m craving. Because if he doesn’t… I’ll hurt him. I don’t want to hurt him. I just want to rest. It’s not too much. I would do it for him. I would say goodbye to him while he was still my sweet, darling husband, and not one of those things outside in the street. He has to do it. He has to. I hope I don’t have to beg him.
Player_BricksForTheBoy_USA01=Hey there, bud. What’s your name?
Kadim_BricksForTheBoy_USA02=Kadim.
Player_BricksForTheBoy_USA03=Kadim, I like that name.
Kadim_BricksForTheBoy_USA04=I have a secret.
Player_BricksForTheBoy_USA05=Really? So do I.
Kadim_BricksForTheBoy_USA06=What’s your secret?
Player_BricksForTheBoy_USA07=I’m a GRE agent. What’ve you got?
Kadim_BricksForTheBoy_USA08=Can you get my blocks for me?
Player_BricksForTheBoy_USA09=That’s not really a secret.
Kadim_BricksForTheBoy_USA10=But some of them are downstairs… near the basement. And Mr. Rupert said we’re not ever to go near the basement. Not EVER. But I went down there, just to see…
Kadim_BricksForTheBoy_USA11=…and I heard a scary sound, and I kind of dropped my blocks. They’re kind of… all over. Could you get them back for me?
Player_BricksForTheBoy_USA12=That’s a tall order. But I’ll give it a shot.
Player_BricksForTheBoy_END01=Here ya go, Kadim. All blocks accounted for.
Kadim_BricksForTheBoy_END02=Thanks. Hey, are you going to tell Rupert about this?
Player_BricksForTheBoy_END03=Will you keep my secret?
Kadim_BricksForTheBoy_END04=That you work for the… Who was that again?
Player_BricksForTheBoy_END05=You’re secret is safe, Kadim. But I’m going to talk to Rupert about those noises in the basement. I heard them too.
Rupert_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG01=Alya is okay. She’s sleeping now. She’ll need some time to fully recover. Thank you again, Mr. Crane.
Rupert_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG02=My wife Jasmine should be back any time now, and since I know how tiring these kids can be, I’m sure you’ll be wanting to move on.
Player_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG03=Not just yet.
Rupert_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG04=But… Well, our supplies are very limited.
Player_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG05=This is too much responsibility for one person, Rupert. I’ve sent for help. They’ll be here soon.
Rupert_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG06=That’s not necessary. Jasmine and I can handle things just fine.
Player_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG07=Rupert. I was downstairs.
Rupert_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG08=Oh… I see.
Player_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG09=I’m sorry, Rupert.
Rupert_BricksForTheBoy_01DLG10=Sometimes in those noises… I think I can still hear a tiny trace of her voice.
Rupert_Dungeons_USA01=I was hoping it would be over by now.
Rupert_Dungeons_USA02=But I couldn’t do it. My wife! My beautiful, beautiful Jasmine.
Player_Dungeons_USA03=This has to end.
Rupert_Dungeons_USA04=I would let her kill me before I would lift a finger to harm her.
Player_Dungeons_USA05=Give me the basement key.
Rupert_Dungeons_INP01=Have you been down there yet? I… I’m almost afraid to ask…
Rupert_Dungeons_INP02=I am ashamed that I failed her so badly.
Rupert_Dungeons_INP03=Please give closure to us both. I beg you.
Rupert_Dungeons_END01=Did you find her? Were you… able to help her?
Player_Dungeons_END02=She has peace now.
Rupert_Dungeons_END03=Th-thank you. From both of us. I hope, somewhere, I may find forgiveness for what I did. For what I… couldn’t do.
Girl01_UglyMonster_USA01=Are you really leaving?
Player_UglyMonster_USA02=I’m afraid I have to, sweety. But some friends are coming to help you guys out. They’ll be here really soon.
Girl01_UglyMonster_USA03=What if the troll gets them?
Player_UglyMonster_USA04=What troll?
Girl01_UglyMonster_USA05=There’s a giant troll down in that parking lot. He makes lots of very scary noises, so it’s hard to sleep.
Player_UglyMonster_USA06=Well, that’s no good. Maybe I’d better chase him away. We can’t have trolls in the parking lot, can we?
Girl01_UglyMonster_USA07=No sir.
Troy_FanZone_05DLG01=Tell me what’s happening.
Player_FanZone_05DLG02=I’m in the Fan Zone. This place is a trap. Keep people the hell out of here.
Troy_FanZone_05DLG03=Understood. Now take your own advice, and get out of there.
Voice_FanZone_05DLG05=To anyone who can hear this: Your situation is dire. I’ve killed women and children here.
Voice_FanZone_05DLG06=I can offer you death in exchange for your medicine, food and drinking water. Come to me…
Player_FanZone_05DLG07=I think I’m going to have to deal with this one, Troy. Crane out.
Voice_FanZone_05DLG08=Ahh! So you wish to challenge me! Excellent. Take the elevator, and it will bring you straight to me.
Voice_FanZone_06DLG01=To anyone who can hear this: Your situation is quickly deteriorating.
Voice_FanZone_06DLG02=I’ve killed so many I can no longer remember them all. But they were all weak. You are weak, so you will die.
Voice_FanZone_06DLG03=To anyone who can hear this: I’m going to cut off your head... but not right away, of course.
Voice_FanZone_06DLG04=I used to kill people quickly, but now I take my time. I’m more… methodical. I think that’s a sign of maturity, don’t you?
Voice_FanZone_07DLG01=To anyone who can hear this: I’m going to cut out your ear drums, so you won’t hear anything. You will die in total silence. Not to worry, I will hear your screams for you, so they won’t go to waste.
Voice_FanZone_08DLG01=To anyone who can hear this: I was left behind by cowards, but I’ve survived by awakening my natural predatory abilities.
Voice_FanZone_08DLG02=Here I am ruler. Here I am king. Here you will die!
Voice_FanZone_08DLG03=To anyone who can hear this: You’re almost mine. How accommodating of you to bring yourself to me. I barely have to get out of my chair to kill you.
Voice_FanZone_08DLG04=Hurry along. One mustn’t rush, but one must not dawdle either. Fate awaits.
Voice_FanZone_08DLG05=To anyone who can hear this: You can stop fearing now. Your problems are nearly over. I have resolved the problems of so many. Now I will solve yours.
Voice_FanZone_09DLG01=All are guilty!
Voice_FanZone_09DLG02=All are weak!
Voice_FanZone_09DLG03=All are cowardly!
Voice_FanZone_09DLG04=All must die!
Player_FanZone_END01=Troy? It’s Crane.
Troy_FanZone_END02=You alright?
Player_FanZone_END03=Some psycho’s been luring people into the Fan Zone and hunting them. Must be 15 to 20 bodies down here.
Troy_FanZone_END04=Is he dead?
Player_FanZone_END05=Dead as I can make him. Crane out.
Player_Prophecy_04DLG01=And there’s the red trail. Well, he’s either clairvoyant, or I’m being setup.
Player_Prophecy_04DLG02=The deceitful nine must be a room number then…
Player_Prophecy_05DLG01=107 is the last room.
Player_Prophecy_06DLG01=Deceitful nine. Of course.
Player_Prophecy_06DLG02=Now how do I find the key in all this mess?
Player_Prophecy_07DLG01=This was Rais’s room. He must have set up shop here when the epidemic first began.
Player_HackingJob_01DLG01=Seems like the power is out. I won’t find a goddamn thing until it’s fixed.
Player_HackingJob_01DLG02=I need to find another way in.
Player_HackingJob_01DLG03=That looks promising…
Player_HackingJob_01DLG04=Rest in peace, pal. You’ve made your choice.
Player_HackingJob_01DLG05=The elevator is busted. I better start climbing.
Player_HackingJob_01DLG07=The power is back on. Now I need to find the Water Resources Department…
Player_HackingJob_01DLG08=The power is back on. Let’s get to work…
Player_HackingJob_01DLG09=Hmmm… I need to figure out where the printers are.
