Player_Explosives_37DLG01=Okay, Jade, I’m inside.
Jade_Explosives_07DLG01=Check the classrooms. That’s the most likely place for them to store supplies.
Jade_Explosives_07DLG02=They should be marked somehow. Military jargon is pretty straight forward, so it shouldn’t be hard to notice.
ExplosivesBandit01_Explosives_09DLG01=Who the fuck are you? Guys! There’s somebody in here!
Player_Explosives_10DLG01=I can’t get through that way…
ExplosivesBandit02_Explosives_11DLG01=Hurry up! We don’t have all day for this shit, and this is the last place I want to be at night!
ExplosivesBandit02_Explosives_11DLG02=Did any of you idiots think to check the basement? Of course not, because the key is still up here! Get your shit together!
ExplosivesBandit03_Explosives_12DLG01=Burn in hell, you bastard!
ExplosivesBandit02_Explosives_13DLG01=We got somebody in here that don’t need to be! Find him and kill him!
Jade_Explosives_14DLG01=Turn that damn thing off! We’re gonna have walkers swarming towards the school!
Player_Explosives_14DLG02=I’m working on It, Jade.
Jade_Explosives_17DLG01=For fuck’s sake, Crane! Turn that damn alarm off or you’re going to get overrun!
Jade_Explosives_17DLG02=Find the janitor’s office. The switch ought to be in there.
Player_Explosives_20DLG01=Jade, no luck with any Antizin. Looks like we’ll have to talk about… that other option. I still have Classroom C to search, though.
Jade_Explosives_20DLG02=The basement’s pretty big. Find the key. I’ll meet you down there.
Player_Explosives_21DLG01=Locked. Great…
Player_ShowMeMoney_01DLG01=Empty. Of course.
Erol_ShowMeMoney_02DLG01=Sorry, Crane. I had no choice.
Player_ShowMeMoney_02DLG02=Karim said I was a fool to trust you.
Erol_ShowMeMoney_02DLG03=It’s not what you think. I would have taken you with me.
Erol_ShowMeMoney_02DLG04=I contacted the evac when you were off getting the paint. I had to tell who would be on board, so I gave them your name.
Erol_ShowMeMoney_02DLG05=Now, I don’t know who you are, but they knew, and they said you were a no go.
Erol_ShowMeMoney_02DLG06=So I had to send you on that phony money run. There is no money-at least none worth mentioning. I’m sorry, Crane. But I’ve got to get my family out of here.
Erol_ShowMeMoney_02DLG07=Go to the rooftop, and you’ll find some things you can use. It’s not what I promised, but it’s the best I can do. Thank you for what you did for us, Crane. Good luck.
