RaisWarehouseGuard01_CHT01=Who the hell are you?
RaisWarehouseGuard01_CHT02=What do you want, motherfucker?
RaisWarehouseGuard01_CHT03=What are you looking at, huh?
RaisWarehouseGuard01_Chapter01_01ONC01=Tower trash.
RaisWarehouseGuard02_CHT01=More fresh meat.
RaisWarehouseGuard02_CHT02=You don’t belong here. You better turn around.
RaisWarehouseGuard02_CHT03=I’d say you took a wrong turn somewhere.
RaisWarehouseGuard02_Chapter01_01ONC01=Are you here to join? Shit. You wouldn’t last a minute.
RaisWarehouseGuard03_CHT01=If you’re looking for trouble, you found it.
RaisWarehouseGuard03_CHT02=That’s a sweet-looking mouth you got, boy.
RaisWarehouseGuard03_CHT03=You’re one of the Brecken’s little pups, aren’t you?
RaisWarehouseGuard03_Chapter01_01ONC01=You and I could be reeeeaalll good friends.
RaisWarehouseGuard04_CHT01=You got the kind of face that needs punching.
RaisWarehouseGuard04_CHT02=Make one move and you’re dead.
RaisWarehouseGuard04_CHT03=Watch yourself.
RaisWarehouseGuard04_Chapter01_01ONC01=Hey, guys! Look at this chickenshit!
RaisWarehouseGuard05_CHT01=Let me give you some advice: do what Rais says, if you like your head on your shoulders.
RaisWarehouseGuard05_CHT02=Just stay away from me and you’ll be fine.
RaisWarehouseGuard05_CHT03=Do what you need to do and get out of here.
RaisWarehouseGuard05_Chapter01_01ONC01=Get to the point when you talk to him. Rais doesn’t like to play around.
RaisWarehouseGuard06_CHT01=What?
RaisWarehouseGuard06_CHT02=Get out of my sight.
RaisWarehouseGuard06_CHT03=Who the fuck are you?
RaisWarehouseGuard06_Chapter01_01ONC01=I don’t know who you are and frankly, I don’t give a shit. So stay out of my sight.
Karim_Antennas_USA01=There you are. Rais said you’d be coming by. I’m Karim.
Player_Antennas_USA02=Crane.
Karim_Antennas_USA03=An American. I have an uncle there. Lives in Texas. You from Texas? You a cowboy?
Player_Antennas_USA04=I’m from Chicago.
Karim_Antennas_USA05=Okay, Al Capone, we’ll be in constant contact over the radio. That way I can make sure you get where you need to go.
Player_Antennas_USA06=And where’s that exactly?
Karim_Antennas_USA07=You’re going to be climbing antenna towers and switching on shortwave radio modulators.
Karim_Antennas_USA08=Most of my men are too slow, too fat, or too drunk to climb a tower like that without killing themselves.
Player_Antennas_USA09=And if I do this, I’ll get the Antizin?
Karim_Antennas_USA10=That’s between you and Rais. I know better than to speak for him. Just don’t fail. He doesn’t handle disappointment very well.
Rais_Antennas_END06=Well! You not only did the job Karim asked of you, but you made it back in one piece. Bravo.
Player_Antennas_END07=Can I get some Antizin now?
Rais_Antennas_END08=Did you think I would be satisfied so easily? You still have plenty to prove.
Player_Antennas_END09=Look… we really need the drugs. Let me have them now, and then I’ll come back and do whatever.
Rais_Antennas_END10=You’ll get Antizin when I SAY you get it. Not one second before.
Rais_Antennas_END12=But as I have established, I am not unreasonable. Do all that I ask of you, and I will give you not one… but two crates of Antizin.
Player_Antennas_END14=All right. Fine. What do you want me to do?
Rais_Antennas_END16=This will be a bit different from your exploits on the antennas. It will require a bit more… persuasion.
Rais_Antennas_END17=The imposing of one’s will. The creation of one’s own rules. That is what makes a man.
Rais_Antennas_END18=Do you live by your own rules, Crane? Or are you merely someone else’s puppet? I believe I know the answer.
Rais_Antennas_END19=Talk to Karim, before I decide you are no longer worth the trouble.
Karim_Courier_USA01=Ah, my friend. Rais likes you, I can tell…
Player_Courier_USA02=How?
Karim_Courier_USA03=Because you are still among the living. The task at hand is as easy as can be. You simply have to make a few pickups from some nearby settlements.
Player_Courier_USA04=Which ones?
Karim_Courier_USA05=The first is Jaffar’s Wheelstation. It’s just east of here.
Karim_Courier_USA06=But bear in mind, not everyone you talk to today will be in a… cooperative state of mind. I’m sure you can be convincing, though, no?
CIN_RaisRequest_02_Player=Yes I do. Now it’s time for you to give me what you promised. Two crates of Antizin.
IntrudersBandit01_Warehouse_08DLG01=I can’t believe how hard those bastards fought back.
IntrudersBandit02_Warehouse_08DLG02=They were all willing to die to save one dried-up old bastard.
IntrudersBandit01_Warehouse_08DLG03=Yeah, but he was working on a cure to the virus, wasn’t he?
IntrudersBandit02_Warehouse_08DLG04=Is that why Tahir wanted him?
IntrudersBandit01_Warehouse_08DLG05=Who the hell knows…
IntrudersBandit02_Warehouse_08DLG06=With Tahir it’s usually about the money…
Player_Warehouse_09DLG01=Shit… it’s broken. Maybe I could pry it open…
Player_Warehouse_09DLG02=And we’re in…
IntrudersBandit01_Warehouse_10DLG01=Tahir can be reasoned with, but Rais? He is fucking crazy.
IntrudersBandit02_Warehouse_10DLG02=I don’t care if he’s crazy or not. I just don’t want him pissed off at me.
IntrudersBandit02_Warehouse_12DLG02=Shit! That’s one of Brecken’s runners!
Player_Warehouse_13DLG01=And where are you, old friend?
Player_Warehouse_14DLG01=Brecken, I couldn’t find Zere inside. The building looks empty, though.
Brecken_Warehouse_14DLG02=There’s an underground level… Maybe he’s down there.
Player_Warehouse_15DLG01=Oh, yeah, no way this could go wrong.
Player_Warehouse_16DLG01=God damn it…
Player_Warehouse_20DLG01=Crane here. I could REALLY use some GRE support right now.
Ministry_Warehouse_20DLG02=That’s too bad, Agent Crane. This is the Ministry of Defense.
Player_Warehouse_20DLG03=The fuck-? What the hell is going on? What happened to the GRE?
Ministry_Warehouse_20DLG04=The Global Relief Effort’s position here has been… diminished. We are in charge now, and we have declared Harran a Code One Target Zone.
Player_Warehouse_20DLG06=Wait, wait, wait… Just hang on! You can’t just carpet-bomb this place! There are still hundreds of innocent people in here! Maybe thousands!
Ministry_Warehouse_20DLG07=Irrelevant. We’re doing this to protect BILLIONS of lives. Surely you can understand that.
Player_Warehouse_20DLG08=Okay, okay - just listen! There’s this scientist in here named Zere, and he’s been doing research on a cure! And he’s really close! I’ve seen the research! If you bomb the city…
Ministry_Warehouse_20DLG10=… Acknowledged. The chances of one scientist in a wrecked city coming up with useful results are negligible at best, but… you have 48 hours.
