Player_Looting_12DLG01=Oh shit…
Nazim_BringGalib_01DLG01=Who the hell are you?!
Player_BringGalib_01DLG02=Your brother is paying me to find you.
Nazim_BringGalib_01DLG03=Well, you’ve definitely earned your money. But Osman is in danger. Rais’s men know where he is now.
Nazim_BringGalib_01DLG04=It’s a lot to ask, but could you take him a message?
Nazim_BringGalib_01DLG05=Tell Osman that he’s got to get out of there, and that he should meet me at the Red Wall stash. He’ll know what that means.
Player_BringGalib_01DLG06=Alright, I’ll tell him Now, we’d both better get out of here.
RaisSoldier_DeathNote_06DLG01=We cut power to the lift, Karim! Just in case!
Player_DeathNote_03DLG01=Karim, it’s Crane. Drop your weapon or you’re dead.
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG02=What the hell’s your problem? This doesn’t concern you!
Player_DeathNote_03DLG03=Sorry, Karim, but Erol Asani is my concern.
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG04=You’re working for him? You’re a fool!
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG05=I was his bodyguard. Okay? After everything got fucked up and they built the wall, we got overrun. He got bitten on the leg…
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG06=I took him to Randall, the only doctor I knew in the Slums… and we cut it off. Clean.
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG07=It was the only way… he would’ve turned if we hadn’t done it. But the stubborn bastard never forgave us. So, we parted ways.
Player_DeathNote_03DLG08=So why are you trying to track him down now?
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG09=Early on, the authorities evac’ed all the political bigwigs out of the zone. Erol told us there was a chopper on the way to take us out with him.
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG10=Then he got bitten, and with all the shit that happened after that, we missed the flight.
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG11=But after you turned on the transmitter, we heard Erol asking for evac. And a couple of days ago somebody responded… from outside!
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG12=The old bastard’s got a flight out, and I want a seat on it.
Player_DeathNote_03DLG13=What about Rais? Does he care about this guy?
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG14=Not a rat’s ass. This was my business. I just want to get out of Harran.
Player_DeathNote_03DLG15=Well, it looks like you won’t be making that flight, huh?
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG16=That had already dawned on me. But I’d like to walk out of here.
Player_DeathNote_03DLG17=Look, if I see you again, I’m going to assume the worst. You got it?
Karim_DeathNote_03DLG18=Fair enough. Good luck, Crane. You’re going to need it.
Wife_PerfectMurder_01DLG01=Aziz, is that you?!
Player_PerfectMurder_01DLG02=Hello?
Wife_PerfectMurder_02DLG01=Where’s Aziz? Something smells funny around here. Do you smoke? There’s head cheese in the fridge, if you like. Shall I put out a platter?
Wife_PerfectMurder_02DLG02=You know what gives me hiccups? Talking too fast. Uh-oh, I’ve got hiccups!
Wife_PerfectMurder_03DLG01=HICCUP!
Wife_PerfectMurder_04DLG01=Do you know Patty in 12A? She has irritable bowel syndrome. It sounds funny, but there’s nothing funny about it.
Wife_PerfectMurder_05DLG01=I’ll tell you what’s funny: The Lump on Abra Bazzi’s nose! It looks SOOO stupid. She should get it removed, but she won’t because she’s too cheap.
Wife_PerfectMurder_06DLG01=I’m thinking about getting a tattoo. Something small and tasteful, like a battleship that says, "Don’t mess with the Queen." That’s me. I’m the queen.
Wife_PerfectMurder_07DLG01=Are you a continental? Of course, I’m married, but Aziz is not exactly Omar Sharif. Now there’s a man. So’s George Clooney. What was I talking about?
Wife_PerfectMurder_08DLG01=Now I remember! Would you like to hear me sing?
Wife_PerfectMurder_08DLG02=Oh Danny Boy. The pipes, the pipes are calling…
