Spike_PlayerProgression_ElectricFence_DLG01=Hey Kyle-how do you feel about playing with electricity? You know to treat it with respect, right? I hope so, because we’ve got some new electric fence traps set up.
Spike_PlayerProgression_ElectricFence_DLG02=When you activate them, the biters will literally fry! Just make sure you’re far enough away that you don’t get zapped yourself.
Spike_PlayerProgression_LightTraps_DLG01=Listen up, we’ve got some new light traps set up around the zone. According to Brecken, you’re one of us now, so I suppose you can use them.
Spike_PlayerProgression_LightTraps_DLG02=If you get in trouble-scratch that, WHEN you get in trouble-lead your pursuers into one of these traps and just watch them burn.
Spike_PlayerProgression_CarBomb_DLG01=Okay, it’s like this: you can rig the car traps to detonate now. It attracts biters, and goes off when they get closer. It’s nothing flashy-more concussion than heat-but it gets the job done.
Spike_PlayerProgression_Clothes_DLG01=I’ve got a few items for you. Should protect you a little better than what you’re wearing now.
Spike_PlayerProgression_Clothes_DLG02=Here’s your new outfit. Give it a look.
Spike_PlayerProgression_Clothes_DLG03=I think you’ll like this new outfit. Much better protection this time.
Spike_PlayerProgression_Shield_DLG01=How’re you holding up out there? Staying in one piece? Well, this should help: it’s a shield I put together. Figured you could be my guinea pig.
Spike_PlayerProgression_Shield_DLG02=It’s a little on the bulky side, but it’ll offer a good bit of protection from biters.
Spike_PlayerProgression_Shield_DLG03=Now listen-I’m proud as hell of that thing, seeing as it’s my first one and all, but if you break it, I’ve left some more with the quartermaster. So you can get a new one from him.
